realstrategic.com 2015-05-19

# Privacy Policy | Real Strategic, Inc

**Real Strategic is committed to protecting your privacy. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Real Strategic website and governs data collection and usage. By using the Real Strategic website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.**

##### **Collection of your Personal Information**

Real Strategic collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home andor work address and or telephone number. Real Strategic also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.

There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Real Strategic. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used by Real Strategic for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Real Strategic website.

In the event that you contact us for customer support through the website, we may also request that you provide additional User Information relevant to the support requested by you. Users are under no obligation to provide such information. However, we cannot guarantee that we can provide customer support in the event that relevant information related to the use of our products or services is withheld. We may retain communications relating to customer support, and/or information drawn from such communications, for statistical and/or reference purposes.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Real Strategic public message boards or forums, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: Real Strategic does not read your private online communications with others.

Real Strategic encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from Real Strategic so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. Real Strategic is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the Real Strategic and Real Strategic family of websites or the use of your information by such outside websites.

##### **Use of your Personal Information**

Real Strategic collects and uses your personal information to operate the Real Strategic website and deliver the services you have requested. Real Strategic may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Real Strategic and its affiliates. Real Strategic may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services.

Real Strategic does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Real Strategic may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, Real Strategic may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. Such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Real Strategic, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

Real Strategic does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.

Real Strategic keeps track of the websites and pages you visit within Real Strategic, in order to determine what Real Strategic services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Real Strategic to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

Real Strategic websites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Real Strategic or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Real Strategic (including enforcing this agreement); and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Real Strategic, or the public.

##### **Use of Cookies**

The Real Strategic website use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies are not used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Real Strategic pages, or register with Real Strategic site or services, a cookie helps Real Strategic to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Real Strategic website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Real Strategic features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Real Strategic services or websites you visit.

If you provide Real Strategic with user information, you have the following rights with respect to that information:

[bullet_list]

  * To review the user information that you have supplied to us
  * To request that we correct any errors, outdated information, or omissions in user information that you have supplied to us
  * To request that your user information not be used to contact you
  * To request that your user information be removed from any solicitation list that we use
  * To request that your user information be deleted from our records and
  * To opt out of being solicited by this website or third parties

[/bullet_list]

If you request that your user information be deleted from our records, there may be a brief delay in our processing that request, while verify that the request is valid and originates from you as opposed to an unauthorized third party. If you request that your information be deleted, we reserve the right to terminate and or limit your access to the Real Strategic website.

To exercise any of these rights, please contact us at info@Real Strategic.com.

##### **Security of your Personal Information**

No method of safeguarding information is 100% secure. Real Strategic uses a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Real Strategic secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

##### **Changes to this Statement**

Real Strategic will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Real Strategic encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Real Strategic is protecting your information. When such a change is made, we will update the “Last Updated” date above.

##### **Enforcement of this Privacy Statement**

If you have questions regarding this statement, you should first contact us at realstrategichelp@gmail.com. If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or we have not addressed your inquiry to your satisfaction, you should then contact us at [realstrategichelp@gmail.com](mailto:realstrategichelp@gmail.com).

##### **Contact Information**

Real Strategic welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Real Strategic has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Real Strategic at [realstrategichelp@gmail.com](mailto:realstrategichelp@gmail.com). We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
